响应式设计，这我造！(⊙o⊙)哦~~ 这不但能调整你的浏览器，
Responsive design, I know. [LAUGH] It's fun to resize your web browser and
还能去看看哪些站点有积极的调整，哪些仍然在使用死大笨的水平滚动条。
see which sites resize gratefully and which sites remain defiantly large with
而响应式设计并不仅仅只在web端。
gross horizontal scroll bars. But responsive design is not just for
如今，手机与平板电脑之间的界限正在消失。
the web. Today, the lines between phones and tablets are disappearing. So
如何将你的程序UI扩展到多屏已经变的越来越重要了。
it's important to think about your UI will scale in our multiscreen world.
千万不要被打倒哦！这就像是在网页设计响应布局一样，
Don't be overwhelmed. Just like designing responsive layouts for the web,
建立一个合理灵活并符合常见设备规格的布局。
build your layouts to be reasonably flexible or within a common device size.
你可以设置选项，提供可选择的不同尺寸规格的布局。
Then you can set break points, providing alternative layouts for
这样一来，
those various sizes. Think about it this way,
小屏手机，大屏手机，平板电脑，大型平板电脑就都可以使用了。
small phone, large phone, medium tablet, and large tablet.